[
   {
      "task":
        {
          "prompt": "I need to concentrate ___ my homework.",
          "optionA": "at",
          "optionB": "on",
          "optionC": "of",
          "rightOption": "b"
         }
   },
   {
      "task":
        {
          "prompt": "He's really bad ___ cooking.",
          "optionA": "at",
          "optionB": "for",
          "optionC": "with",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
   },
   {
      "task":
        {
          "prompt": "I've always had difficulty ___ math.",
          "optionA": "against",
          "optionB": "from",
          "optionC": "with",
          "rightOption": "c"
       }
   },
   {
         "task":
        {
          "prompt": "Mark applied ___ a scholarship.",
          "optionA": "for",
          "optionB": "on",
          "optionC": "to",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
   },
   {
         "task":
        {
          "prompt": "I'm incapable ___ playing sports.",
          "optionA": "to",
          "optionB": "about",
          "optionC": "of",
          "rightOption": "c"
       }
   },
   {
          "task":
        {
          "prompt": "They have to work ___ this project.",
          "optionA": "at",
          "optionB": "on",
          "optionC": "with",
          "rightOption": "b"
       }
   },
   {
         "task":
        {
          "prompt": "I need a moment to recover ___ the shock.",
          "optionA": "from",
          "optionB": "about",
          "optionC": "against",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
   },
   {
         "task":
        {
          "prompt": "These sneakers are not suitable ___ jogging.",
          "optionA": "at",
          "optionB": "for",
          "optionC": "of",
          "rightOption": "b"
       }
   },
   {
           "task":
        {
          "prompt": "This book had a profound influence ___ me.",
          "optionA": "at",
          "optionB": "for",
          "optionC": "on",
          "rightOption": "c"
       }
   },
   {
         "task":
        {
          "prompt": "I've always struggled ___ Physics at school.",
          "optionA": "with",
          "optionB": "on",
          "optionC": "about",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
   },
   {
         "task":
        {
          "prompt": "She asked ___ the condition of the house.",
          "optionA": "about",
          "optionB": "on",
          "optionC": "in",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
   },
   {
         "task":
        {
          "prompt": "I'm certain ___ it.",
          "optionA": "at",
          "optionB": "about",
          "optionC": "in",
          "rightOption": "b"
       }
   },
   {
         "task":
        {
          "prompt": "The hotel has the advantage ___ being cheap.",
          "optionA": "at",
          "optionB": "on",
          "optionC": "of",
          "rightOption": "c"
       }
   },
   {
         "task":
        {
          "prompt": "This town is specialized ___ receiving tourists.",
          "optionA": "in",
          "optionB": "on",
          "optionC": "about",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
   },
   {
         "task":
        {
          "prompt": "The event was crowded ___ young people.",
          "optionA": "in",
          "optionB": "on",
          "optionC": "with",
          "rightOption": "c"
       }
   },
   {
           "task":
        {
          "prompt": "They deserve the credit ___ planning the trip.",
          "optionA": "with",
          "optionB": "for",
          "optionC": "of",
          "rightOption": "b"
       }
   },
   {
           "task":
        {
          "prompt": "She just glanced ___ the newspaper.",
          "optionA": "at",
          "optionB": "on",
          "optionC": "of",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
   },
   {
           "task":
        {
          "prompt": "We were furious ___ the hotel manager.",
          "optionA": "with",
          "optionB": "against",
          "optionC": "about",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
   },
   {
           "task":
        {
          "prompt": "Everyone was surprised ___ the low prices.",
          "optionA": "at",
          "optionB": "in",
          "optionC": "of",
          "rightOption": "a"
       }
   },
   {
           "task":
        {
          "prompt": "I trust ___ your ability.",
          "optionA": "at",
          "optionB": "on",
          "optionC": "in",
          "rightOption": "c"
       }
   }
]